You always get that, Chizuru.
千鶴はいつもそれ買うよね
そんなにおいしいの
Is it really that good?
100% fruit juice.
果汁100パーセント
Mixed Juice
いろんな果物が入って　お得な感じなのだー！
With all of the different fruits in here, I feel like I'm getting a good deal!
Mixed Juice
味見させて
Let me have a taste.
あー　やめろよ
Don't do that!
だったら　ゆっきーのリンゴジュースもよこせよ
Give me some of your apple juice, then!
Give me some, give me some!
But you have apple juice in your mixed fruit juice.
よこせ
いやいや　リンゴは千鶴のミックスジュースにも入ってるじゃないですか
No buts!
いやいやじゃねえよ
Hey, you!
おい　こら　返せ
Give it back!
My 100% fruit juice!
俺の果汁100パーセント
How do you guys keep up the 100% stupidity all the time?
なぁ　なんでお前らって常にそうあほ100パーセントを維持できんの
100%, damn it!
Damn it! You bastard!
It's not that great.
生かな
100パー
100%!
相も変わらずの僕たちの毎日
Our unchanging daily routine.
緩やかに過ぎる日々も楽しいけれど
While we enjoy these quiet days,
the slightest change causes great excitement.
ちょっとした変化は僕らを妙にわくわくさせる
遅くなってすみません　ちょっと忘れものして
Sorry I'm late.
I forgot something.
職場体験のリストなんですけど
It's the workplace experience list.
Workplace experience?
職場体験？
はい
Yes.
Regarding Work Experience Placement
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Oh, yeah. We got a sheet like that.
あー　何かもらったね　そんな紙
I haven't really looked at it yet, though.
まだよく見てないけど
毎年二年が行くんだっけか　それ
Is that the field trip second years take each year?
Just look at this.
見てくださいよ　ここ
Our old kindergarten, Hidamari Kindergarten, is on the workplace experience list.
僕らが通ってた陽だまり幼稚園が職場体験リストに入ってるんですよ
あっ　本当だ
You're right.
So why don't we all go
to Hidamari Kindergarten together?
ね　だから皆で陽だまり幼稚園に行きませんか
ふーん　いいね　それ
Good idea.
今もいるのかな
I wonder if Kaori-sensei's still there.
香織先生
Don't you?
何だよ　俺にふんなよ
What?
Don't ask me!
ガキん時の話だろう　あれは
I was just a kid.
I wonder if they have more playground stuff now.
遊具とか増えてるのかな
かもしれないですね
They might.
ね　千鶴
Hey, Chizuru...
Oh, go right ahead.
あ　どうぞ
Don't worry about me. Have all the fun you want.
俺のことは気にしないで　盛り上がっちゃってくださいよ
部外者はここで大人しく見てますから
Outsiders will quietly observe from over here.
Stop your annoying pouting.
お前面倒くせえすね方すんなよ
I'm not pouting.
別に　確かに俺だけは皆と幼稚園一緒じゃないし
I'm the only one who attended a different kindergarten.
なんか疎外感感じちゃってますけど
I do feel a little out of the loop,
but I wouldn't pout over something like that.
それぐらいじゃすねませんよ　別に
Your lip is sticking out even as you say that.
そう言ってる口がもうとんがってるんですが
千鶴君　千鶴君も一緒に行きましょうよ
Chizuru-kun.
Chizuru-kun, come with us.
だって俺そこの卒園生じゃないし
But I didn't go there.
そんなの関係ないですよ
That's not important.
I want to go with you.
僕は千鶴君と一緒に行きたいですよ
春ちゃん
Shun-chan...
Thank you!
ありがとう　やっぱり春ちゃんだけだよ
You're the only one, Shun-chan!
You're the only one who hears my inner thoughts!
俺の心の声に気付いてくれるのは
You actually said them out loud.
実際に出てんだよ　声に
それじゃ　皆陽だまり幼稚園に決定ということで
It's decided, then.
We're all going to Hidamari Kindergarten.
Yup.
はい
I'm so excited!
わぁーい　楽しみだな
Yeah, me too.
うん　楽しみだね
要の恋がどんな展開を見せてくれるの
I wonder how Kaname's love life will unfold.
I told you that I don't feel that way any more!
だから今は違うって言ってんだろう
Many seasons have come and gone,
and although much time has passed,
何度となく季節が過ぎて
随分と時が経ったはずなのに
we always recall our childhood.
いつもあの頃が蘇る
あの場所へ戻るのは楽しみでもあり
We were both excited and somehow apprehensive about visiting the kindergarten.
どこか不安でもあり
わー　懐かしいな
This brings back memories.
It hasn't changed one bit.
昔と全然変わってないっ
Was the jungle gym always this small?
こんなにちっちゃかったっけ　ジャングルジム
The kindergarten hasn't changed, but we've certainly grown.
幼稚園は昔のままなのに
僕らが大きくなっちゃったんですね
おーおー　ちっちゃい子はこの寒い中よく遊ぶね
Those kids don't even let the cold stop them from playing.
You're right.
そうですね　もうすっかり冬なのに
It's the middle of winter, too.
Huh? What'd you say?
え　何だって
要　何　緊張してるの
What's with you, Kaname? Are you nervous?
まあ　無理ないよ
You can't blame him.
もうすぐ憧れの香織先生
He's about to meet his beloved Kaori-sen—
いいか　お前ら
Listen up, you guys.
You better not say a word about it.
ぜっていそのこと言うんじゃねえぞ
If that little monkey finds out about this...
子ザルにばれるようなことがあったら分かってんだろうな
you understand what'll happen, don't you?
Okay.
はい
So this is your kindergarten!
え　ここが皆の育った幼稚園か
千鶴君　どこ行くんです
Chizuru-kun, where are you going?
I'm just going to look around!
ちょっと探険
Ow.
いて
千鶴君　大丈夫ですか
Chizuru-kun, are you all right?
You little... Who are you?
こんの　誰だ　こら
ん　お前こそ誰だよ
No, who are you, illegal trespasser?
この不法侵入者が
おい　お前　あぶねえだろうが
Hey, that's dangerous!
サルはどうでもいいが
Not that I care what happens to this monkey.
We're just here for our workplace experience—
俺たちはただ職場体験で
話を聞け
Listen to me!
ちょ　ちょっと
I don't listen to evildoers!
悪者の言い分なんて知ったこっちゃねえぜ
危ない　危ない
Really, we're not!
本当に違うんです
We're— Ow!
僕ら　いて
My hair's stuck...
髪の毛が枝に
春ちゃん
Shun-chan!
W-W-Wait!
ちょ　ちょっと待っ
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
You should be more careful, Miss.
ったく　気をつけろよ　姉ちゃん
A woman's hair is her life.
髪の毛は女の命だぜ
一応僕男なんです
I'm actually a man.
What?
それにしても　なんだかかわいそうなことしちゃいましたね
Either way, it seems we've done something unfortunate.
Huh?
もう　いいじゃねえか　どうせもう枯れてんだから
Who cares?
It's already dead.
It's not dead.
枯れてるんじゃないですよ
春になったらまた新しい葉っぱが出るんです
It'll grow new leaves in the spring.
It will?
そうなのか
おら
やりたい放題やりやがって
Gotcha, you brat!
You think you can do whatever you want?
捕まえるぞ　ワルガキ
We'll turn you in to your teacher!
先生に突き出してやる
放せよ
Let go of me, stupid monkey and stupid four-eyes!
このクソザル　クソメガネ
Hey, guys...
Ow, stop struggling!
ちょっ　二人とも
要君　春君　悠太君　祐希君
Kaname-kun, Shun-kun, Yuuta-kun, Yuuki-kun!
Hey!
おいこら　ちゃんと掴んでろよ要っち　逃げられちゃったじゃん
Keep a tight grip on him, Kanamecchi!
You let him get away!
皆よく来てくれたわね
Thank you all for coming.
香織先生
Kaori-sensei!
It's good to see you again.
お久しぶりです
今日はよろしくお願いします
Thank you for having us today.
こちらこそ　よろしくね
No, thank you.
I-It's...
久しぶりです
good to see you.
要君も大きくなったわね
Kaname-kun, you've grown so much.
Yes, he's got quite the attitude now—
ええ　もう態度ばっかり
Hey, hey!
はいはい　俺皆のフレンド　橘千鶴っす
I'm everyone's friend, Tachibana Chizuru!
It's nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします
あら　よろしくね
My, nice to meet you.
I can't believe how beautiful you are.
先生　きれいっすね　びっくりしたっす
Do you have a boyfriend...
今恋人とか
What, Kanamecchi?
何　要っち　挨拶してただけじゃん
I was just getting to know her!
And by that you mean you were hitting on her!
挨拶という名のナンパだろうが　ったく
Okay, everyone!
はい　皆
These students from Homare High School will be your teachers today!
今日一日穂稀高校の兄ちゃんたちが皆の先生になってくれます
Play nice, children!
皆仲良遊びましょうね
Okay!
はーい
I need to go see the head teacher.
私園長先生に呼ばれてて　行かないといけないんだけど
Take care of them while I'm gone.
ちょっとよろしくね
Oh, okay.
あ　はい
No problem. Piece of cake.
大丈夫っす　楽勝っす
You have antennae!
お兄ちゃん触角生えてる
He's a rhinoceros beetle!
カブトムシだ
私お嫁さんになってあげる
I'll be your wife!
No fair!
That's a little fast for me.
いや　いきなりお嫁さんはちょっと
ちゃんと段階踏みたいんで
I want to take things slow.
Hey, why are your faces the same?
ねね　なんでお兄ちゃんたち顔が一緒なの
Everything about us matches because we're friends.
なんでもお揃いなんだよ　仲良しだから
You're such a cute girl!
お姉ちゃん可愛い
ちょ　ちょっとまっ　なんで
What? W-Wait...
W-Why?
おい　メガネ返しやがれ　おもちゃじゃねえんだぞ
Hey! Give me back my glasses!
They're not a toy!
逃げろ
Run!
Let's go shopping today.
今日はお買いものに行きましょう
いいわね　素敵
That sounds wonderful.
I want new clothes!
私　新しいお洋服ほしい
あら　このワンピースなんか似合いそうよ
This dress would look good on you.
Super Lightning Blizzard!
スーパーライトニングブリザード
Fight back with your own special attack!
なんか必殺技出して抵抗して
O-Oh, right!
はい
Strawberry Milk Cream Special!
イチゴミルククリームスペシャル
It's not supposed to be a dessert.
デザートじゃないんだよ
はい
Right.
ね　あなた　あたしたち結婚して二年目よ
Darling, we've been married for two years.
I want a child.
あたしそろそろ子どもがほしいわ
子作りですか
You want a child?
それはちょっと犯罪になるので　年齢的に
I think that would be a crime, age-wise.
Stop playing house as if it's real.
お前ままごとでリアルに返してんじゃねえよ
Should we have a boy or a girl?
男の子がいいかしら
女の子がいいかしら
How about this, Sono-chan?
じゃ　園ちゃん　こうしよう
この子が息子
This is our son.
What?
は　無理無理無理
No, no, no! There's no way I'm playing house!
俺ままごととか絶対無理
If you don't think you can,
you'll never be able to.
できないって決めつけてるうちは　一生できないよ
That's fine with me!
一生できなくていいわ
それじゃ　家族揃ったところで
Now that the whole family's here, let's have dinner!
晩ご飯にしましょう
さあ　召し上がれ
Eat up.
Om nom nom.
You're the best cook in the world.
うん　母さんのご飯は世界一おいしいよ
Thank you, dear.
まあ　あなたったら
You too, Kaname.
ほら　要も
ちゃんとやらないと
You have to do it properly. Come on.
ほら　ほら
職場体験なんだから　ちゃんとやらないと
You're supposed to be taking this workplace experience seriously.
Om nom nom.
パク　パクパク
It's so good.
おいしいな
You bastard!
てんめ　今笑ったろう
You laughed, didn't you?
Of course I didn't.
嫌だな　違うよ
ご飯が喉に詰まって
Some food got stuck in my throat.
We're not actually eating!
リアルに食ってねえだろうが
How dare you speak that way to your parents!
親に向かってなんなのその口の聞き方
お母さん悲しいわ
I'm so upset!
Stop being so dramatic! We're only playing house!
お前はままごとで迫真の演技繰り出すな
Beep, beep!
Out of the way, out of the way!
The second son's here! Beep, beep!
次男坊様のご帰還じゃ　ブーブー
We don't need you bringing your nonsense into this game!
おめえも明らかにままごとに不必要な設定しょってくんじゃねえよ
I refuse to play a character that isn't at least this badass!
このくらい影あるキャラじゃねえと　俺には役不足だぜ
I don't remember raising such an terrible son!
お父さんはそんな親不孝者生んだ覚えはない
Pow.
ばきん
Honey, stop!
いや　あなたやめて
そりゃ生んでねえだろうよ
He's not your son.
うるせえな
Shut up.
あなた　落ち着いて
Honey, calm down!
お前も一緒にやるか
Do you want to play, too?
なんでこの俺が　お　おままごとなんかしなきゃならねんだよ
Wh-Why would I play h-house with you?
ダッセー
Lame!
There you go again, Ken-chan!
あ　また健ちゃんそういうこと言う
Now, now.
まあまあ　よいではないか
It's not so bad.
What do you think you're doing?
何すんだよ　放せよ
Let go!
ちゅうことで
This guy will be your third son.
こいつここの三男坊な　よろしく
Say hi.
三男
Third son?
三人兄弟は多いかも
Three might be... too many.
Huh? Why?
どうして
だってご飯の食器が足りないもん
We don't have enough tableware.
Having a third might be problematic.
三人目は困るかも
Then, I'll be the first son!
じゃ　俺長男やる
いきなりやる気だな
That's the spirit.
But the guy with the glasses is our first son.
え　でも長男はメガネのお兄ちゃんだし
I'm much better suited for the job than him!
あんなのより　俺のが全然合ってるよ
おめえなんか犬で十分だ　メガネ
You can be the dog, four-eyes!
Dog?
犬
Go be a good guard dog!
せいぜい番犬でもやってろ
You brat, I'll show you...
んのガキ　言わせておけば
Stop!
止めて　うちの子にひどいこと言わないで
Don't say such terrible things to my child!
Stop being so over dramatic!
だから　おめえはいちいち迫真の演技をしてんじゃ
What are you doing?
ちょっと何すんのよ　健ちゃん　ひどい
Ken-chan, you're awful!
けっ　やっぱくだんねえよ　ままごとなんか
This is stupid!
Playing house is so boring!
あー　つまんねえ
あーあ　要が番犬やらなかったせいだ
It's Kaname's fault for not being a guard dog.
Hey!
おい　俺のせいかよ
You're blaming me?
You And I
Bathroom, bathroom...
トイレ　トイレ
あ　春ちゃん
Ah, Shun-chan...
What's wrong?
どうしたんですか　皆
I'm exhausted.
あー疲れた　体力持たねえよこれ
I won't make it.
I can't keep up with kids these days.
なんかもう最近の若い子の乗りって付いていけないよね
I know. Maybe they're already the new generation.
ね　時代はもう次の世代かな
Hey, you've all gotten old fast.
ちょっと皆　いきなり老け込んじゃってますよ
僕らの時だって結構わんぱくだったり
We were naughty and precocious when we were little, too.
おませなこと言ったりしてたじゃないですか
あ　そうね
Yeah.
I guess so.
そうかもね
What? Was Kanamecchi in love with someone?
何
要っち好きな子でもいたわけ
え　そうなの
You were?
Oh, but kids these days are much naughtier... Right?
あー　でもやっぱり今の子の方が
もっと輪をかけてわんぱくと言うか　ね
Yeah, they are!
そうだよ　特にあの健ちゃんとかいう悪ガキとかな
Especially that brat, Ken-chan.
健ちゃん
Ken-chan?
Between when we first got here and playing house...
最初の時といい　ままごとといい
I've had enough of his attitude!
なめんのもいい加減にしろうっつんだよ
僕にはそんなに悪い子には見えなかったけどな
He didn't seem like such a bad kid to me.
きっとやさしい子ですよ
I'm sure he really is a good kid.
素直になるのがちょっと苦手なだけで
He just doesn't know how to show it.
Okay, okay.
はいはい　ったく　これだからお花畑は
Everything's a bed of roses to you.
あ　なんかバカにしてません
Are you making fun of me?
皆ここにいた
There you all are.
Kaori-sensei.
香織先生
It's almost snack time. Would you like to join us?
これからおやつの時間なんだけど
皆も一緒にどう
香織先生　よく男子トイレに堂々と入ってこれますね
Kaori-sensei, I'm amazed you didn't think twice about coming into the men's room.
What if we were in the middle of something?
真最中だったらどうするんですか
Huh?
Which means she doesn't see us as men. Not now and not back then.
つまり　男として見られてないってことだよ
今も昔も
Shut up!
うるせえな
なんだお前　食わないのか
You're not going to eat?
Huh? It's got nothing to do with you, four-eyes.
おめえには関係ねえだろう　メガネ
You brat!
お前　本当　一一つっかかって
You're always trying to start fights.
俺はお前嫌いなんだよ
I don't like you.
I hope Kaori-sensei turns you down soon!
おめえなんかさっさと香織先生にフラれちまえ
Th-That's not...
そ　そんなんじゃ
Don't get the wrong idea.
勘違いすんなよ
園ちゃんが抱きついたのは
Sono-chan didn't hug you because she l-loves you.
す　好きとかそういうんじゃねんだからな
ままごとなんだからな
You were just playing house.
自惚れんなよ　タコ
Don't let it go to your head, octopus!
Oh, right. I see.
あー　はいはい　なるほどね
H-Hey.
おい
Ken-chan?
健ちゃん
やる
You can have this.
何それ
What is that?
C-Cookies.
く　クッキー
Whose?
誰の
Wh-Who cares whose they are?
誰のでもいいだろう
Just eat them!
いいから　食え
Ken-chan, I bet you stole them!
あー　健ちゃん　人の盗ったでしょう
I didn't...
違う
Sensei!
先生　健ちゃんが人のおやつ取った
Ken-chan's stealing other people's cookies!
Again? Bad boy.
ええ　また
いーけないんだー
Bad boy, bad boy, bad boy...
いーけないんだー*7
健ちゃん　ひどい
Ken-chan, you're so mean!
先生　健ちゃんが僕たちのも
Sensei, Ken-chan ate our cookies!
おい　待てってお前
Hey, hold on...
Kaname-kun, are you all right?
要君　大丈夫ですか
You little twerp! You won't get away with this!
このやろう
もう絶対許さねえ
Kaname-kun!
要君
畜生　あいつどこに
Damn it. Where'd he...
なんだこれ
What is this?
春になったらまた新しい葉っぱが出るんです
It'll grow new leaves in the spring.
そうなのか
It will?
Hey!
おい
'on't follow ee!
ついて来るんじゃねえよ
I 'on't wanna be 'elled at by oo!
てめなんかに説教されたくねえよ
Hey.
おいってば
'o away!
あっちいけ
頬張りすぎだ　あほ
You put way too much in your mouth, stupid.
きっとやさしい子ですよ
I'm sure he really is a good kid.
He just doesn't know how to show it.
素直になるのがちょっと苦手なだけで
That's disgusting!
あ　きったね　お前人の靴の上にぼとぼと落としてんじゃねえよ
Don't dribble all over someone's shoes!
Sheesh.
ったく　行くぞほら
Let's go.
Where are we going?
行くってどこにだよ
Huh? You should know better than anyone else.
It's fine! It's fine!
いい　いいっていい
It's not fine!
いいじゃねえよ
You have to do the right thing...
お前な　こういうとこちゃんとしておかねえと
It doesn't matter!
いいんだよ　もう
I'm a bully!
俺意地悪だし　どうせもうとっくに嫌われてんだよ
She already hates me.
There's nothing...
今更
Let's go.
行くぞ
Sono-chan, you're in the middle now.
じゃあ　次園ちゃんが真ん中ね
Okay.
Kagome kagome, the bird in the cage...
かごめかごめ
籠の中の鳥は
Sorry.
わりぃ
いついつ出やる
When will you come out?
What?
なに
夜明けの晩に
In the evening of the dawn,
the crane and turtle slipped.
鶴と亀が滑った
後ろの正面だあれ
Who's the boy standing behind you?
Ken-chan?
健ちゃん？
あ　本当に健ちゃんだ
It really is you!
H-H-How'd you know?
なん　なんで
だって　甘い匂いがしたもん
Because I smelled something sweet.
なんかね　健ちゃんがあたしの近くにいる時
Sometimes, I smell sweets when you're near me.
たまにおやつの匂いがするの　なんでかなって
It's so weird.
意地悪なのに　変なのって
I don't know why, since you're so mean.
ごめん
Sorry.
Sorry about the cookies... and your house game.
クッキー食べちゃって　あとおままごとも
ごめん
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
Kaori-sensei, thank you for letting us come today.
それじゃ　香織先生
今日はお世話になりました
ううん　こちらこそとても楽しかったわ
No, thank you. I had so much fun.
またいつでも遊びにいらっしゃい
You're welcome to come back any time.
はい
Okay.
Oh? What is it, Ken-chan?
あら　どうしたの　健ちゃん
そっか　お兄ちゃんたちにお別れ
Oh, right.
You're here to say goodbye—
ごめんね　要君　大丈夫だった
I'm so sorry, Kaname-kun!
Are you okay?
Uh, fine.
あ　はい
Come now, Ken-chan!
もう　コラ健ちゃん
See ya, four-eyes!
じゃあな　メガネ
んの　じゃあなじゃねえよこのクソガキが
Don't give me that, you little twerp!
Those boys were fun, weren't they?
おもしろいお兄ちゃんたちだったね
They're just annoying.
煩いだけだぜ　あんなの
I wish we could play house with them again.
また一緒におままごとしたいな
そしたらまたあのかっこいいお兄ちゃんのお嫁さんになろうと
I'd be that cool guy's wife again.
健ちゃん　あのメガネのお兄ちゃんには何の役してほしい
Ken-chan.
What do you want the guy with the glasses to be?
Huh?
兄ちゃん
My brother.
I had so much fun at Hidamari Kindergarten.
いやあ　楽しかったな　陽だまり幼稚園
You all went there, huh? Lucky.
皆はあの幼稚園に通ってたの　いいにゃー
There weren't any kids that precocious while we were there, though.
俺たちの時代にはあんなませてる子はいなかったけどね
There were. Two of which I knew.
いたよ　俺の身近に二人ほど
Let's go again sometime.
また皆で行きましょうね
You guys go.
行けよ　俺は行かねえぞ
I won't go near that brat again.
あんな可愛くねえガキのとこ
You're still mad about that?
もう　まだ怒ってるんですか
はたから見てると要君と健ちゃんちょっと兄弟みたいでしたよ
You two looked like you could be brothers.
やめろよ　全然似てねえよ
What?
Cut it out. We're nothing alike.
そんなことないですよ
That's not true.
好きな子に一生懸命な姿なんか
He was just as passionate about the girl he liked...
as you were about Kaori-sensei.
香織先生好きだった頃の要君にそっくりでしたよ
Really? Kanamecchi, were you really?
そうだったの？　っちって昔そうだったの？
Shun, I told you not to tell him.
春　お前ぜってー言うなっつったよな
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Huh?
Oh!
あー　違うんです　今のはわざとじゃなくて
That didn't count. I didn't mean to!
まじかまじで
I can't believe it was him who spilled the beans.
まあ　これ意外な人がぺろっと言っちゃったね
Chizuru, you shouldn't laugh so much.
千鶴　あんまり笑ったらダメだよ
若気の至りってやつなんだから
It was just youthful indiscretion.
This is great!
Don't treat someone's first love like a mistake!
お前も人の初恋人生の汚点みたいにいうんじゃねえよ
あの頃の僕たちがいたのは　陽だまりのような場所
It was as though we were standing in a beam of sunlight.
寒い冬も　熱い夏も　穏やかな温もりに変えてくれた場所
It changed cold winters and hot summers into a comfortable warmth.
I wonder how far and how long we'll travel together from that place.
僕たちはあの場所からどこまで
いつまで一緒に歩いていけるのだろう
The Sunshine Song
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
You taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me